#### Contact

Hitec City, Hyderabad 8299018281 (Mobile) aadil.srivastava01@gmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/aadil-srivastava-788442139 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Python

Machine Learning

Microsoft Office

#### Certifications

Natural Language Processing with Python

Serverless Machine Learning with Tensorflow on Google Cloud Platform

Serverless Data Analysis with Google BigQuery and Cloud Dataflow

Deep Learning Specialization

Google Cloud Platform Big Data and Machine Learning Fundamentals

# **Aadil Srivastava**

Machine Learning at ValueLabs | Google Cloud Certified Professional DE

Hyderabad

## Summary

Deep Learning practitioner specialising in Natural Language Processing & Computer Vision.

Built & deployed scalable ML solutions across a variety of domains. Love to learn about the advancement in field of Data Science and try to apply those learnings for solving real-world Data Science problems.

## Experience

ValueLabs
Machine Learning at ValueLabs
December 2019 - Present (9 months)
Hyderabad

#### Pluto7

Machine Learning Engineer May 2019 - December 2019 (8 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Tata Consultancy Services
Assistant System Engineer
October 2017 - March 2019 (1 year 6 months)
Mumbai, India

## Education

Uttar Pradesh Technical University

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science · (2013 - 2017)

International Hindu School, Varanasi AISSCE (2008 - 2012)